import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

List<Map<String, dynamic>> Question = [
  {
    'id': 1,
    'question': "1.The 227 year old 'Nawab Saheb Ki Haveli' is Iocated at.",
    'A': 'Hyderabad',
    'B': 'Jaipur',
    'C': 'New Delhi',
    'D': 'Agra',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
  {
    'id': 2,
    'question': "2.How many districts are there in Gujrat?",
    'A': '31',
    'B': '32',
    'C': '33',
    'D': '34',
    'answer': 'C',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
  {
    'id': 3,
    'question': "3.The first month of Saka year is.",
    'A': 'Vaisakh',
    'B': 'Paush',
    'C': 'Jyeshtha',
    'D': 'Chaitra',
    'answer': 'D',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
  {
    'id': 4,
    'question': "4.Delhi became capital of India in.",
    'A': '1910',
    'B': '1911',
    'C': '1916',
    'D': '1923',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
  {
    'id': 5,
    'question': "5.World Health Day is observed on.",
    'A': 'Apr 7',
    'B': 'Mar 6',
    'C': 'july 5',
    'D': 'Apr 28',
    'answer': 'A',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
  {
    'id': 6,
    'question':
    "6.Which of the following is observed as Sports Day every year?",
    'A': '29 April',
    'B': '29 August',
    'C': '29 October',
    'D': '29 july',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
  {
    'id': 7,
    'question': "7.On____is Replublic Day of india?",
    'A': '2 May',
    'B': '15 September',
    'C': '26 January',
    'D': '15 January',
    'answer': 'C',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
  {
    'id': 8,
    'question': "8.The International Literacy Day is observed on.",
    'A': 'May 2',
    'B': 'Nov 28',
    'C': 'Sep 8',
    'D': 'Sep 22',
    'answer': 'C',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
  {
    'id': 9,
    'question':
    "9.In the game of ludo the discs or tokens are of how many colours?",
    'A': 'One',
    'B': 'Two',
    'C': 'Three',
    'D': 'Four',
    'answer': 'D',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
  {
    'id': 10,
    'question': "10.On____is Independence Day of india?",
    'A': '15 August',
    'B': '8 September',
    'C': '26 January',
    'D': '14 January',
    'answer': 'A',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.white,
  },
];